Huh?
What did you say, Luffy?!
Let's tame the octopus
and make him pull our ship!
No way!
Take a good look!
No, you don't have to take
a good look since it's huge!
Oh, it's big!
We're dead!
It must've been around for
several hundred years!
The Kraken appears in many
myths in the world -
it's like a visionary creature!
It has no bones and I'm a
skeleton without any flesh...
It's the polar opposite of me.
I don't care!
You're quite good.
You can't see this kind of thing often, so...
Sketching? How relaxed?!
I'll help you but do you
have any plan, Luffy?
The problem is that we're in the sea.
No. No. No.
The problem is the size of it.
It would be dangerous
even if we were on land.
What's wrong with them?
This is the kind of situation
when everybody agrees to
run away at full speed!
Shift the helm to the south!
Hey, Nami, go straight towards the octopus!
Don't be a fool!
--The octopus will...
--Whoa, whoa, Nami-san. I'm here for...
...here for...
...for you!
You held it! Good job!
Thanks to the rehabilitation
and to Nami for wearing a coat.
It's dangerous to be on this ship!
I've got to protect myself!
Something's coming from behind!
Brother!
They came back!
Coribou! Guys!
--We're gonna save my brother!
--Yes!
You came back to save me, huh?!
Don't do it!
--The coating popped!
--That ship is even bigger than Sunny!
Oh... Guys!
--They look like a school of jellyfish.
--Shut up, Roronoa! Cut it out!
It's coming!
--It's too big!
--How can we fight against it?!
Third Gear...
No!
You'll break the bubble!
Chicken Voyage!
Can we... get away somehow?!
Don't do anything! I'll beat it!
No! You're gonna break the bubble!
Listen! If you wanna fight against
it that much, here is an idea!
What is it? Tell me.
Okay, that's good!
That's the extra-vehicular
Flutter Kick Coating!
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
As long as you're in it, you can
fight as you want even in water!
If I let these fools do whatever
they want, I'll be in danger too!
You shouldn't have done that, stranger!
We wanted to run away!
Now, they're gonna fight!
I told you guys to run from the beginning
but that Captain-san won't listen!
Would you rather they fought on this ship?
Okay, good luck! Go far away!
This rope is annoying.
Stay away from this ship!
Alright.
--Okay, let's go!
--Yeah!
Huh?
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
You'll be separated!
Nami-san's worrying about me!
You guys! Draw his attention for me!
I'm gonna beat him with one strong blow!
I could beat him right away!
You can't cut him!
I want the octopus as a pet!
Are they okay?
Stay as far away as you
can! Even a millimeter...
But it's attacking us!
Move aside, guys!
Franky...
...Rocket Launcher!
--It deflected the tentacle!
--How powerful!
--Got it!
No, another arm!
And... another one!
Why does it keep coming after us?!
Why does he keep attacking us?!
It's gonna hit us!
Guard Point!
Guard Boost!
They got a hard hit!
Are you guys okay?
Th-That was close!
H-He did it!
--Well done!
--Yeah, Chopper!
We're gonna hit the mountain!
We're gonna hit a sea mount!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Huge hands!
What big hands!
--Yes!
--Nice, Robin! You saved us!
--That's our Robin! We're saved!
--Yes!
--Nice, Robin! You saved us!
Good. Even underwater, I managed it
because it was only a brief moment.
Good. Although I'm in water,
I was okay because it
was just a brief moment.
They did great.
Alright, it's my turn!
Good. Even underwater, I managed it
because it was only a brief moment.
Here is the new technique!
Gear Three!
Third Gear!
Color of Arms Hardening!
Armament; Hardening!
What is that?!
The sea is sapping my strength!
I feel weak because of the sea!
Damn that octopus! Is it trying to stop him?
That damn octopus!
Is it trying to stop him?
Blue Walk!
What? Sanji-san left his bubble!
Whoa, Sanji-san got out of the bubble!
That's really fast!
He's like a Fish-Man! That's so cool!
Never mind that! Look at that speed!
He's like a Fish-Man! Cool!
I've been running and running
I ran and ran...
...from those abominations for two years.
in order to get away from those hideous people for 2 years.
Compared to them,
the monster is nothing.
It actually looks rather cute to me.
Diable Jambe!
Bien Cuit...
...Grill Shoot!
...Grill Shot!
Three-Sword Style technique;
Crossing the Six Paths!
Three Sword Style Secret Move!
Hey hey, Zoro! Sanji! You can't cut his arms!
Whoa-whoa! Zoro! Sanji!
It can't pull our ship without its tentacles!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
He blew it away!
He knocked it out!
He's gotten so much stronger!
Even while he's in the sea...
Hey! Something is in there!
A shark?
--A shark?
--Isn't that shark wearing something?
That's fairly big.
What?
They've been swept away
by the downward current!
Oh no! Follow them! We have to stay together!
Okay!
--I don't wanna die here!
--You've got to be kidding me!
--You're still here?
--You're too calm!
My eyes are spinning! But I don't have eyes!
Keep the yard level! Hard to Port!
We're gonna crash into the continental shelf!
I got it!
Don't lose your concentration,
or the ship will wreck!
What?!
Don't get thrown off!
Stay in the center of the current!
Alright!
It's really fast!
This is fun!
Usopp!
Oh, ow, ow, ow!
I'm alive!
What? Why are you all so glum?
Oh I know! You guys can't
do anything without me...
It's so cold here!
We can't find Luffy and the
other two. We got separated.
What?!
I hope they haven't been
shredded to pieces by the monster.
Your imagination is terrifying...
It's too dark - I wanna look for
them but I can't see anything!
I'm not good with darkness.
I feel something, don't you?
We probably submerged around 7,000 meters.
Even the Shark Submerge can't
take the pressure this deep.
Are we near the Fish-Man Island?
Maybe they got there already...
Camie-chan said it's located
at 10,000 meters below sea level.
We have to submerge 3,000 meters more?!
All they have is a small bubble.
Even if they're alive,
there isn't enough air so it's dangerous!
That's why I told them to
attach the safety rope!
We won't accomplish anything
standing around like this.
Let's look for them. I now have a search light.
What?!
Is it your eyes?!
Franky...
...Nipple Lights!
Why there?!
Let's get away!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Where did you go?
Come back!
Luffy-san! Zoro-san! Sanji-san!
In this vast, submerged expanse,
the Sunny Eyes don't help that much.
We're stuck...
The darkness is stirring up our anxiety.
In fact, we're not getting
anywhere. What should we do?
We can't stop the ship so try
not to overlook anything.
Oh, it's a jellyfish! There's a
massive jellyfish above us!
That's huge! You're right!
They're twinkling! Like stars in the night!
That's beautiful!
Oh, a tentacle!
D-Do you wanna be my friend?
Don't touch it, Chopper!
It's probably venomous!
Oh no! A little...
...Coup de Burst!
Wh-What?!
The jellyfish got eaten!
Oh, we lost some air.
Better than getting eaten!
Coup de Burst is a weapon that
shoots a fair amount of air.
But since we're in the water,
we only have a limited amount of air.
So when we shoot the air
out, the bubble shrinks!
I see. But it makes me nervous
to see the bubble shrinking.
That fish that got bitten
turned upside down!
So they contain a neurotoxin as I thought.
The deep sea's scary! It's dark too...
There are a lot of fish with
white eyes... It's creepy here!
Since the deep sea is always dark,
there are many creatures with rudimentary eyes.
So they can't see well.
Fools! See this? Come here!
But there are some with developed eyes too.
What's that? How can I see things without eyes?
Do you people wanna know why?
The answer is... Tum, tum, tum, tum, tum...
...a secret!
Are you talking to yourself?
No problem. I'm used to being lonely.
Hey! Stop fooling around and look for them!
Why did I get hit?
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji! Where are you?!
Oh?
This rope must be...
Everyone.
Have you seen that pirate guy?
Oh yeah, he's still here!
I totally forgot about him.
Where did he go?
I haven't seen him since we got this deep.
Maybe he got thrown off
during the downward pull.
That could be it!
His hands and legs were tied up so
he couldn't hold on to anything.
Well but...
...he untied himself. See?
Th-Then, he's somewhere
on the ship? Where is he?
He's got to be hiding somewhere...
What?!
Oh no...
I'll sneak into the girls' room--
if that's what you want, honey.
Damn! We have enough problems already
but now we have to look out for him too.
Who cares! He's not that strong anyway.
It's great.
Those formidable 3 who were fighting
against the Kraken went missing.
There's no way they could have
survived after getting lost
with just those bubbles to protect them.
It's a shame that I couldn't kill Straw Hat
but I can prove that he's dead by killing
these crewmembers and taking their heads.
But don't rush, Caribou!
You can't rush!
If I kill them here, there's no one else to sail the ship.
They navigate the ship pretty well.
As soon as you get to the Fish-Man Island,
you all will be dead!
Here he is!
--Oh no! Shoot! Dammit!
--Now he can't get away.
How did he get in there?
We weren't paying attention. If he
wasn't so stupid, we could be in danger now.
His body wasn't taking form.
It has melted like mud.
--Like mud?
--Yeah, I'm sure it's a Devil Fruit power.
He must've eaten a Logia-type fruit.
He was only pretending to be caught.
Hey, get me out of here, mister!
Mister in swimshorts!
I'll become your servant!
What's the matter, Chopper?
I don't know. I feel hot all of the sudden.
I can't stand the heat.
It's hot! What happened?
Wh-What's this? Smoke?
It's blocking our view forward!
Smoke from the sea floor? Why?
It's...
It could be...
Hydrothermal deposits!
--A volcanic area in the sea!
--What?!
Look, you can see that there
were volcanic eruptions here!
Let's get away from here!
If it erupts, we're gonna die!
It's hot... It's hot...
Something's after us!
Carnivorous Tubeworms!
We have no choice.
A little Coup de Burst!
Faceless Crabs!
I don't even know what they are!
A little Coup de Burst!
The deep sea's scary!
Luffy and the others can't survive here.
I'm starting to get sad.
I finally got to see him after 2 years...
Cut it out! They're not gonna die so easily!
I used Coup de Burst little by
little but we lost so much air.
What is that?! It's so bright!
Is that the Fish-Man Island?
Do you think Luffy and the others are there?
We haven't submerged
another 3,000 meters yet.
"WHO-ARE-YOU?"
Hey! What are you sending
the flashing signals with?!
--Do you see anything?
--No, it's still too bright.
Oh no!
It's an angler! He tricked us!
We were fooled by the deep-sea hunter!
That was close!
We're totally trapped! Can we get away...?
What is it this time?!
I-Is it a human?
What the hell is it?!
A monster in the sea that looks like a man...
It's a Sea Bonze!
He's gonna capsize the ship!
That?!
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
Don't eat ships! How many
times do I have to tell you?
Captain Vander Decken-sama won't like this!
D-Did he help us?
Let's go! We have to get away
anyway! He is a monster too!
--Dead men tell no tales, they have no desire.
--Is that...
--...me?
--In the dark land where even crows can't fly.
Dead men don't need jewels on their finger.
You can't even see
somebody's sorrow in the dark.
Look for it! Look for it!
Sunken treasures are mine!
I am the richest person in the
world - Captain Vander Decken!
Don't tell me it's...!
Even in the sea?!
A ghost ship?!
You shouldn't be so scared!
I turned! For no reason!
We thought that you were
a ghost at that moment!
Th-That is the real one! Look at that sail!
The infamous Flying Dutchman!
It shouldn't exist in the real world!
It happened several hundred years ago.
One stormy day, the captain of the
pirate ship suddenly lost his mind
and killed all his crew by throwing
them into troubled waters one by one!
And he even cursed the gods!
The name of the captain was Vander Decken
and the ship was the Flying Dutchman!
The gods got mad at him
and set him adrift forever
under constant tortured!
And the ship right in front of us is
Captain Vander Decken's haunted ship!
Could this be...
Ankoro! Wadatsumi!
We can't seize their treasure
if you eat the ship
so knock it down!
I got it!
--Oh no, the Sea Bonze is...
--He's our enemy after all!
--Franky, use Coup de Burst!
--I can't! The fuel has run out!
I have to fill up with
cola in the energy room!
We don't have time!
--No!
--He's gonna get us!
Kraken!
The Monster of the Arctic--Kraken?
You bastard!
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
Good job!
Hey!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
I'm glad that you're all alive!
What were you doing?!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
We've been looking for you guys!
They're so high-maintenance. They got lost!
He needs rehab with less stimulating pics!
Hey! Wake up, Wadatsumi!
Avenge yourself! Get back at it!
Well, Sanji's bubble and mine
popped so we got into Zoro's.
I thought I was gonna die!
Don't make us worry!
Alright, here's a song to
celebrate your return.
Lots of space!  There's no place like home!
Luffy! I was scared!
You all have an amazing ability to survive.
I can't believe it!
You really tamed the monster octopus?
And are you gonna use the Kraken?
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like
experienced people do!
Right, Surume?
That's a squid snack!
Surume!
The Kraken is an octopus but
he named it Surume, oh yeah!
Alright, draw the Sunny, Surume!
Well, instead of making him draw the ship,
we have to make sure that
he's not gonna smash it up.
Captain, the pirate ship is...
Don't let it get away! Go after it!
Yeah!
What is it?
This is no good, Captain Vander Decken!
Oh no, the undersea volcano's gonna erupt!
What?!